They tell me sing the high note They tell me wear
the red dress They never ask me what I wrote They
only wanna see the press
I bring my chorus, my melody They pat my head and
disagree They turn to him Now that's a sound And
I'm just standing in the background Am I ever
gonna break through? Am I ever gonna get my due?
Or am I just a girl in a band? A pretty picture
holding your hand They say these artists be the
greatest Know your role and keep your place But I
am more than what you see I'm fighting just to be
me Am I ever gonna break through? Am I ever gonna
get my due? Or am I just a girl in a band? A pretty
picture holding your hand But the music's in My
blood, the scent, the key, the flood You can
erase the fire My voice is getting higher Am I
ever gonna break through? Am I ever gonna get my
view?
Or am I just a girl in a band Where I'm just a pretty
picture holding you in?
Just give in Just give in